SOOKIE:
Bill and Eric are here
to blow up the place.
If we don't get out,
we're all gonna die.
You may leave
at any time.
Ah!
(COUGHS)
Eric!
Let the girl go.
The other Eric
is still here.
So what's
the problem?
I love you.
I love him, too.
MARNIE: Kill yourselves,
and she walks free.
I don't think so!
No!
(SHRIEKS)
I'm sorry, okay?
Sookie's fine.
Get out of my sight
before I kill you.
(DEBBIE GASPS)
Alcide...
What the fuck
is goin' on here?
You murdered my brother.
I'm gonna snap your neck
with my own hands.
(GROWLS)
ALCIDE: Sam!
(CRUNCHES)
(CHOKING AND GURGLING)
What did you do?
Debbie Pelt.
ALCIDE: I abjure you.
JESUS:  We need to force
Antonia out of Marnie's body,
and we need Casey's
body to do that.
(CHANTING IN SPANISH)
Oh, G...
Even without your
blood in me, you are
all I think about.
I'm gonna lose
my best friend.
I was tryin' to find
my way out the woods,
and I heard a zap.
Make love to me.
It felt so real.
You want to
know what's real?
There's a waitress
named Holly
who thinks that you're
just the cutest lawman.
(GASPS)
JESUS: Lafayette, did you
hear anything I just said?
Sorry for pushing you into the
magic before you were ready.
Thought I was helping you,
but... I was acting just
like my fuckin'  abuelo .
You were right, baby.
JESUS: This kind of power,
it's not meant for us.
JESUS: It's too strong.
Or we're too weak.
But I swear...
To whatever the fuck is out
there, if you want to lead...
A magic-free life from here
on out, I'm all for it.
Hey.
Are you okay in there?
Yes.
JESUS: Eat your breakfast.
I know it's not fried in
pig fat or whatever secret
deliciousness you use...
But I worked
hard on it.
JESUS: I'll see
you after work.
Lafayette.
Sss... Tut-tut, tut-tut.
(JESUS SCREAMS)
&l When you came in
the air went out
&l And every shadow
filled up with doubt
&l I don't know who you
think you are but before
the night is through
&l I want to do bad
things with you
&l I'm the kind to
sit up in his room
&l Heartsick and eyes
filled up with blue
&l I don't know what you've
done to me but I know
this much is true
&l I want to do bad
things with you
Ow!
&l I want to do real
bad things with you &l
(SIGHS)
TARA: Hey there.
Mornin', Sook.
You get any sleep?
SOOKIE: My nerves are shot.
(SIGHS) After everything
we've been through...
It's a miracle we're
not screamin' in a
padded room somewhere.
Tara, do you think
Gran's in heaven?
(CHUCKLING) Well, I've
always considered myself
to be an atheist.
But if heaven does
exist, I'm pretty sure...
Adele Stackhouse
would be like the
president of it.
Why you thinkin'
about that, anyway?
Marnie channeled Gran.
'Least I think it was her.
She warned me about Antonia.
Told me not to give
my heart to Eric.
Well, she did have all
the sense in the family.
This mornin', I keep
feeling like she's here.
You mean watching over you?
No. I mean, like here, here.
I, I know it's probably
just some residual
weirdness from...
Everything that's
been goin' on...
But, I just can't
shake this feelin'.
Well, if she was here, what
do you think she'd say to us?
To be good to each other.
And wear more sunscreen.
And stop gettin' into
so much dang trouble.
(LAUGHS)
What are we, like,
magnets for fucking
craziness or somethin'?
Lord, I hope not.
Someday, I see myself
growin' old and...
Sittin' on the porch with
my grandbabies on my lap,
just watchin' the sunset.
Hope I get to sit on that
porch wit'cha someday.
Me, too.
(MAXINE CRYING)
Oh... He was a devious
little son of a bitch...
But somewhere in there
he had a good heart.
Not a lot of people got
to see that. I was lucky
enough to be one of 'em.
Well, thank you for comin'.
It would have meant
a lot to my brother.
He said...
"Sam shootin' me was the
best thing that ever happened
to me, Ms. Fortenberry.
"Cause it brought me
to you and the Lord."
Oh... Sweet boy.
'Course, then he
stole a bunch of my
clothes and jewelry.
Even a pair of
my underpants.
And my favorite
church shoes.
Well, I'm sorry.
Um... Nobody taught Tommy
how to love somebody
without hurtin' 'em.
I let him down
that way, too.
My guess is nobody
taught you neither.
We all do the best we
can with what we got.
I'm gonna bring by one of
my...my famous pork rind
casseroles later.
No. No, don't trouble
yourself, Ms. Fortenberry.
Oh, nonsense.
Tommy may not have been
my flesh and blood, but...
He was a son to me.
You call me Mama
from now on.
Uh...
We're all the
family we got left.
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFS)
Hey...
(CHAINSAW CUTTING)
JASON: (TO HIMSELF)
Jason Stackhouse, you
are a good person.
Yes, you are.
Shut up.
(CHAINSAW CONTINUES CUTTING)
HOYT: Hey, Jason!
Hey, buddy. Uh...
JASON: What'cha doin'?
Ah... Oh, just
workin'. You know?
HOYT: (SIGHS) What you doin'?
Just chillin'. You know,
it's a nice day...
Um...
Moist.
Somebody die?
No.
Listen, we gotta
talk, man...
JASON: Uh...
HOYT: Huh?
You mind, you mind puttin'
that thing down first?
Listen...
(STUTTERING) We've, we've
been friends a long time.
You remember...
BOTH: Whoa...
Chicka, chicka,
boom, boom!
(CHUCKLING)
I had sex with Jessica.
(LAUGHING) Yeah...
I ain't jokin'. I wish
I was, but I ain't.
How?
Kind of a weird
question to ask, man.
But if you really
want to know, uh...
Missionary, then doggie,
then her on top.
I mean, it was
nothin' too kinky...
(JASON GRUNTS)
HOYT: No, how could you
do that to me! Not, how
did you fuck my girl.
Listen, I'm sorry, man.
JASON: But, technically...
Hey, technically, she
wasn't your girl no more.
Uh, you, you, you said you
never wanted to see her again.
Yeah, fuck you!
We had a code,
and you broke it!
You coulda had anyone,
anyone you wanted.
I'm not you, man.
She was the only one.
It's... I drank
her blood.
I couldn't think
about anything else.
I tried to fight it, but
it, it just happened.
(JASON GRUNTING)
HOYT: Doesn't just happen.
You make choices.
You make fucked-up, selfish,
piece o' shit choices!
(MOANING)
All right. You made
your point, Hoyt.
JASON: (GRUNTING)
You made your
point... Ahhh! Oh!
Ain't nothin' more important
to you than your dick! Not
even your best friend.
(MOANING)
HOYT: What Jess and I
had, it was real...
And you ain't never gonna
have that, not with her...
Not with anybody, 'cause
there's somethin' inside you
that's... It's just missin'.
Sorry.
(GROANS)
JESUS: Lafayette.
Lafayette, listen to me.
I know you're in there.
Whatever Marnie's making you
do, you have to fight her!
(CHUCKLING EVILLY)
MARNIE: (AS LAYFAYETTE)
You think your little fry
cook can overpower me?
True, his body is younger and
stronger than mine was...
And the magic in him is
potent. Clumsy but potent.
MARNIE: (AS LAYFAYETTE)
He is no Antonia.
Marnie, before Antonia
came along, you were
afraid of your own voice.
You talked to the dead because
they were your only friends.
That's why you wanted
possession so badly, because
you felt lonely...helpless.
I thought you were my
friend. I trusted you.
And you took her
away from me!
She wanted to
leave, Marnie.
Antonia knew you weren't
fighting a righteous war.
She knew that all you really
cared about was power!
(JESUS GRUNTS)
You don't deserve
to speak her name!
Traitor! Antonia was
a hero, a martyr.
Unlike this Lafayette
coward, whom I've had
to take by force!
LAFAYETTE:  Jesus, this
bitch is strong and
seriously homicidal.
MARNIE: (AS LAYFAYETTE)
Call me bitch again, boy...
And I'll cut out your
eyeball and feed it to you.
I can't feel pain,
but you will.
Marnie, please don't hurt him.
I'll do whatever you want.
Just tell me. Tell me
what you want us to do.
I want...
What your grandfather passed
down to you in the blood...
What you've been running
from your whole life...
I want your
magic,  brujo .
All of it.
(LAUGHING)
(FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
SOOKIE: Hey, Arlene.
(GASPS)
Happy Halloween.
Oh, it's Halloween today?
ARLENE: Yup.
Can I interest you
in a hand sandwich?
Oh!
(LAUGHING)
We're zombies.
Zombies are the new vampires.
Didn't you know that?
Wow, no, I did not know
that, but you're severed
toe necklace is super cute.
Thank you.
Is Sam around?
ARLENE: (IN HER MIND)
Oh, Lord, nobody's
told her yet.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
SAM: Come in.
Hey.
SAM: Hi.
I'm sorry about
Tommy. I just heard.
The funeral?
Yeah, well, nobody
knew about it.
My brother didn't have a whole
lot of friends around here.
You do.
Well, I hadn't seen you in
awhile. Figured you had a
lot goin' on of your own.
Oh, Sam...
I was pretty sore after
you fired me and all, but...
I would have been
there for you.
I never fired you. You...
You're the one who didn't
show up for shifts all week.
Not to be a stickler
for details, but...
You told me I was nothing
but trouble and to get my
stuff and get outta here.
You know what?
I wasn't myself that day.
I tell you what. How about we
let bygones be bygones, huh?
Does that mean I can
have my job back?
As long as you can
start right now.
Lafayette's MIA, and with it
bein' Halloween and all...
We sure could use an
extra pair of hands.
Can I have another
uniform? I kinda threw
mine in the trash.
SAM: No uniforms today.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
You want your
job back or not?
SOOKIE: I'm gonna
get you for this, Sam.
SAM: Nobody likes
an angry bunny.
Samhain was Wicca's
greatest holy celebration...
A night we honored and
communed with our dead.
Now, people only
know it as Halloween.
Children feed their fat
faces with candy and...
Run in fear from evil green
hags they call witches.
The vampires have done a
thorough job of demonizing
our most sacred Sabbat...
MARNIE: (AS LAYFAYETTE)
Turning our religion
into a joke.
I agree with you.
Vampires suck.
JESUS: That's why you need
to let go of Lafayette
before they find out.
They'll kill him, Marnie.
Just like they killed you.
If you hadn't betrayed me,
I would still be alive.
Besides, it's the
only host I have.
JESUS: He's not a
host, he's a person.
(STAMMERING) W...with a whole
life and people who love him.
We must all make
sacrifices in time
of war.
I made mine, and now
you will make yours.
You can't trade magic like
fuckin' Pokemon cards!
I would gladly give you
this shit inside of me if I
knew how, but I just don't!
You're afraid.
Yes. And you
should be, too.
Because what's inside
of me is seriously dark.
I'll fight darkness
with darkness.
Who are you
fighting for? Huh?
Antonia's gone, the
circle's broken.
They fear you more than
they fear the vampires!
JESUS: You've turned into
everything that you hate!
Shut up!
You will give me what I
want, or I will wring the
life out of this body...
'Til there is nothing
left but an empty sack.
Okay, enough! Stop it!
I'll do it.
(CRYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(IN SPANISH)  Most Holy
Death, Lady of the Shadows...
Ogoun Ferei, Ogoun
Shango, Nago Piman...
Shows my true face.
(WIND HOWLS)
Give it to me.
(WIND BLOWING)
(GROANING)
Give it all to me.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(MOANING)
(GROANING)
(DEMONIC GROWLING)
(DEMONIC YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(DISTORTED SOUNDS)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
Lafayette...
(LAYFAYETTE GROANING)
I'm sorry.
(DEMONIC GROWLING)
ARLENE: Take off your
mask before you eat now.
Hey, you already had yours.
I'm eatin' for two.
Hey, you better start behaving
yourselves right now...
Or you're gonna be
trick-or-treatin' down at
the trailer park again.
Now, do you want a
bag of empty Coors
cans and food stamps?
Or do you want candy?
It is your choice.
SAM: Coby, Lisa, I want you
to meet my friend, Emma.
Hi, Emma.
Hey.
EMMA: Hey.
That's, uh, quite a costume
you got there, Lisa. What
are you supposed to be?
Jenelle from  Teen Mom 2 .
(SIGHS) Don't even
get me started.
And what are you,
cutie-patootie?
I'm either gonna be a
shapeshifter like my mommy...
Or a werewolf like
my daddy. He's dead.
All righty then.
Gonna get back to work.
PATRICK: Private Bellefleur.
(DROPS DISH BUCKET)
I heard you were dead.
I heard you were crazy.
Well, yeah. That, that's
still true. What the hell
you doin' in Bon Temps?
PATRICK: Just passin' through.
Thought I'd look you up.
(LAUGHING) You
look like shit.
Yeah, I'm a zombie.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, but look...
Wait'll you meet
my wife. Arlene!
Arlene Fowler-Bellefleur...
This is Sergeant
Patrick Devins, United
States Marine Corps.
TERRY: First of the first.
Mrs. Bellefleur,
it's an honor.
Well, it's nice
to meet you, too.
Terry's told me absolutely
nothin' about you.
Perfect. Then I
won't have to lie.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You got time for
a drink with a man
whose life you saved?
Twice. Huh?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
So, does this mean you
aren't mad at me anymore?
It's hard stayin' mad at'cha.
Especially in those ears.
Sam's idea of payback.
Listen, about the other night,
I should have thanked you.
I shouldn't have
lost it like that.
I understand why you did.
Where's Debbie?
Oh, Alcide.
What happened?
You were right about her.
But she changed.
People don't change. They
just find new ways to lie.
I know you don't want to
believe that right now, and...
I didn't come here
to lecture you.
Something tells me
you're about to anyway.
You remember when you said
that if you were smart...
You would have
fallen in love with
someone like me?
Alcide, don't.
People always say
follow your heart.
What if your heart
keeps telling you to do
the same stupid shit...
Over and over again?
What if our hearts
can't be trusted?
If it's our brains we
should be listening to?
You're hurt and angry
right now. I get it.
I've been there.
No. I'm seeing clearly.
Debbie's out of my life,
for good this time.
I'm done with the drama.
I want you to be
done with it, too.
I can't change who I love.
Lord knows I've tried.
Then try harder.
( MONSTER MASH PLAYING SOFTLY)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(CELL PHONE RINGS AGAIN)
Herveaux. Where?
You sure?
I'll be there as
soon as I can.
I gotta go.
Anything I can do?
Just think about what
I said. And try not to
get yourself killed.
I'll work on that.
TARA: Lafayette?
(YELLING) Jesus?
Anybody here?
Hello?
Lafayette?
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
Hey, Sookie. Can I
borrow that lighter?
Holly, you scared the
bejesus out of me.
I'm just a fairy,
honey. Ain't nothin'
scary about fairies.
Yeah, right.
You don't
mind, do you?
Halloween makes me kinda
jumpy, too. Always has.
Wiccans, we call it  Samhain
or the Witches' New Year.
It's the day that the veil
between the living and the
dead is at its thinnest.
You can just feel it
in the air, you know?
Want a puff?
Uh, no, thanks. When
I'm high, I can't shut
out the thoughts at all.
It's like the whole
world's screamin' at me.
Oh, see, it calms my nerves.
Mother Earth's Valium.
So all day, I just had this,
this terrible feeling in my
gut, you know, this dread?
Mmm. I'm sure it's just a
hangover from everything that
happened with Marnie and all.
I, I've had the
same feeling.
(CAR APPROACHING)
Tara? Tara, what, what
is it? What happened?
She's back.
Who's back, honey?
Marnie.
How's that possible? She
died right in front of us.
(CRYING) She killed Jesus.
I think she's
inside Lafayette.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
SOOKIE: (TALKING ON PHONE)
Okay, thanks, Ginger.
Ginger says Eric's been
missin' since nightfall.
Bill?
Not answering his phone.
Oh. I knew it was
in here somewhere.
SOOKIE: You carry
salt in your purse?
Yeah, and sage and a lock
of my Aunt Josie's hair.
It's like a Wiccan
first aid kit.
Hey, any o' you
two got a mirror?
HOLLY: Thanks.
You ever done anything
like this before?
Goddess, no.
Usually, I just...
Light a candle and ask the
spirits to make sure my boys
don't end up in jail or...
Knock somebody up,
but, but so far, that's
worked out okay. So...
Sook, you can't
let them hurt him.
If Bill and Eric find out
Marnie's inside Lafayette...
Yeah, I have a feeling
they already know.
Any idea how to get us out
of this one, Your Majesty?
You could summon Pam.
You could summon Jessica.
Hmmph.
Oh, so you'd sacrifice my
progeny, but not your own?
How very unkingly of you.
I liked you better when
you were brain damaged.
BOTH: Sookie.
As your friend Lafayette
would say, what goes around
comes around, bitches.
Lafayette...and Marnie.
Please don't do this.
After all they've done
to you, you protect them.
Killing Bill and Eric
isn't gonna make any
of that go away.
Revenge will never
bring you peace.
There can't be peace
until there is justice
for me, for Antonia...
MARNIE: (AS LAYFAYETTE) For
all the women you tortured...
(WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
MARNIE: (AS LAYFAYETTE)
And burned for centuries!
All to repress a magic that's
older and more powerful than
your very existence.
HOLLY: (WHISPERING)
Sink all evil. Sink it
to the ground thrice.
Marnie, what
will this serve?
There are millions of us,
more being made every night.
You cannot win.
I'm already dead, vampire.
Thanks to you, I have
nothing left to lose.
(IN LATIN)
Incendia of sanctimonia!
Bill!
(BILL YELLING)
(SOOKIE SCREAMING)
TARA: Sookie! It's
still Lafayette!
I can't just stand
here and let them die.
(ZAPPING LIGHT)
(LAYFAYETTE GRUNTING)
(DEMON GROWLING)
TARA: Lafayette! No!
(BILL AND ERIC YELLING)
Gimme your hands. Now!
(GROWLS)
I'm sorry, Lafayette.
HOLLY: (CHANTING) Spirits
who watch over us...
Friends, family, ancestors,
guardians of the gates...
ALL: (CHANTING) Spirits
who watch over us...
Friends, family, ancestors,
guardians of the gates...
(ELECTROSTATIC ZAP)
(GROWLING)
HOLLY: With this
rite we evoke thee...
Through the veil of  Samhain ,
we call thee forth.
ALL: (CHANTING) We evoke
thee... Through the veil of
Samhain , we call thee forth.
Spirits who watch over us,
friends, family, ancestors,
guardians of the gates.
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(DISTORTED SPIRIT VOICES)
(WIND BLOWING)
(DISTORTED WHISPERING)
(BILL AND ERIC SCREAMING)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
Eric, Bill, don't
you die on me.
SPIRITS: (WHISPERING
CONTINUOUSLY)  Marnie...
(CHANTING)
(GROWLS)
Marnie.
(WHOOSH)
My sister.
You came back to me.
I knew you would.
(BILL AND ERIC
CONTINUE SCREAMING)
Antonia, no!
(SKIN SIZZLING)
(MOANING)
All creatures have their
purpose, even vampires.
How can you say that?
They murdered us!
Their cruelty served its
purpose...to bring you
and I together.
And now I am here
to take you home.
I'm not finished yet.
Oh, yes, you are.
Gran?
Holy Goddess.
Holy shit.
(DISTORTED SOUNDS)
(MOANS)
TARA: Lafayette!
(MARNIE GRUNTING)
I don't want to go.
I am not ready. Please.
I was trapped between
worlds for 400 years.
Lost and driven
mad by my rage.
I do not want
that for you.
And what about
what I want?
Nobody cares what I want!
All my life, I've
been afraid. And
who wouldn't be?
With dead people
murmuring in my ears...
Who are making me
deliver your messages!
Making me into a freak!
A creepy, pathetic,
terrified mess, muttering
to herself in the corner.
But that is not who
you are anymore.
No. That's right. I'm
not afraid anymore.
I've got real power now.
And you want to take
that away from me?
You want them to win?
(GROANING)
Oh, Marnie.
Marnie, can't you
see? Life is pain.
But soon all you have
suffered and feared
will be meaningless.
You will be at
peace. But them...
They'll be stuck
here. Forever.
And there is no
victory in that.
(WIND BLOWING)
(SCREAMING)
That's right, honey!
Let it all out...
'Cause there's no room
for that where we're goin'.
Oh, this fuckin' sucks.
Change is hard.
(SIGHS) Well...
(MARNIE MOANS)
SOOKIE: Gran?
(WHISPERS) Please don't go.
GRAN: I have to, dear.
(CRYING) I'm so lost without
you. I don't know what to do.
Yes, you do. Answer's where
it always is...in your heart.
Bein' alone, it ain't nothin'
to be afraid of, my Sookie.
We're all alone at the end.
(CRYING)
(DISTORTED SOUNDS)
Lafayette. Lafayette,
can you hear me?
Bitch, talk to me.
LAFAYETTE: Mmm.
TARA: You're okay.
You're gonna be okay.
ERIC: Excuse me.
We're feeling a
little crispy up here.
ARLENE: Okay, ya know,
I'll bus the tables,
pour the drinks...
Serve the food and take
out the damn garbage.
You know, no problem!
'Cause, you know, clearly,
I'm the only one who works
here anymore. Flaky skanks.
RENE: (WITH CAJUN ACCENT)
Oh Lord, ain't you a
sight for sore eyes.
(GASPS) Oh God.
This is a dream.
This ain't real.
Okay, wake up,
Arlene. Okay...
Wake up. Ow.
Ain't gonna hurt you,  cher .
I loved you, me.
RENE: You and our baby.
(WHISPERING) Oh God...
&l God said out and
the devil he ran
&l Ain't comin' back
no more no more &l
"Praise Jesus."
(SCREAMS)
I'm here to warn you, girl.
That man, he's bringin'
trouble of the worst kind.
Terry?
Mmm-hmm.
No.
He's good to me and my babies.
I've met the ghosts
of his past.
But, they ain't
gonna rest forever.
TERRY: Arlene!
(GASPS)
Run.
TERRY: What's goin' on?
Hear me? Run!
(SHRIEKS)
(WIND HOWLS)
You all right? Jesus.
(CRYING) Oh God.
Oh!
Somethin' scare ya?
(CRYING)
Shhh.
Terry's here now. Ain't
nothin' gonna get ya.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYS)
&l Little girl little
girl don't you lie to me
&l Tell me where did
you sleep last night
&l In the pines
in the pines
&l Where the sun
don't ever shine
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
I ain't got no candy!
The little shits
egged my house again.
JASON: I will arrest you!
&l Little girl little girl
don't you lie to me &l
Jason? What happened
to your face?
Is this another dream?
'Cause if Hoyt pops out from
under that hood, I'm gonna
knock him the fuck out.
You told him?
(SIGHS) Yeah, I told him.
(ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
He took it pretty well.
Did you hurt him?
I didn't touch him.
Invite me in.
(MOANING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
JESSICA: (MOANING) I don't
want to be your girlfriend.
JASON: What?
I just got out of a
serious relationship.
JASON: Mmm...
My first and only
relationship. I just...
I'm not ready
to commit to you.
JASON: Okay.
Okay, uh...
Kinda wish you would
have told me that, before
I took an ass-kickin'.
I didn't ask
you to do that.
No? But it was the
right thing to do.
And since when is, is Jason
Stackhouse concerned with
doin' the right thing?
You don't know
me very well.
(WHOOSHING)
Fair enough. I'm just
barely gettin' to know myself.
But I don't want to hurt
you, the way I hurt Hoyt.
So I'm asking you, can
this be enough for now?
'Cause...'cause I
don't want it to stop.
(WHISPERING) Uh-huh.
You know what you are?
You're dangerous.
Yes... I am.
(MOANING CONTINUES)
PAM: Where the fuck is he!
I don't know. But Sookie
called looking for him.
PAM: Sookie...
I'm so over Sookie and her
precious fairy vagina and her
unbelievably stupid name!
Fuck Sookie!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHAIR BREAKING)
I've been with Eric
over 100 years.
I've watched him
seduce supermodels
and princesses and...
Spit out their bones
when he is finished.
How can someone named Sookie
take him away from me?
Don't fuckin' touch me.
(CRYING)
Try and get some rest.
I killed him.
No, you didn't.
It wasn't you.
You hear me, Lafayette?
None of this was your fault.
If I can love you...
We're gonna get through this
shit together, just like we
got through everything else.
Okay?
(SNIFFLING)
I'll be right out
there if you need me.
(LAFAYETTE CRYING)
(GURGLING)
(SUCKING)
(SLURPING)
Does it hurt?
If you want us to stop...
No.
(GROWLS)
(MOANING) Okay...
I think that's enough.
You saved my life.
Both our lives.
It was my turn.
ERIC: Thank you.
You don't have to thank
me. I can't imagine a
world without you in it.
Both of you.
I can't stand
this anymore.
It's like being ripped in
half. No matter what I do,
somebody I love gets hurt.
(FANGS RETRACT)
Sookie, I just want
for you to be happy.
And if being with Eric
is what makes you happy...
Then you have
my blessing.
ERIC: See?
It's okay, Sookie.
Bill's fine with it.
Bill had his chance.
He blew it.
He, he lied to you.
To protect me.
And I lied to him
to protect you...
And you've lied to
both of us so many
times, we can't count.
What a mess.
I forgive you.
I know you've loved me every
bit as much as I've loved you.
And we've both hurt each
other just as deeply.
I hope you can
forgive me.
Sookie.
Like I have a choice.
You're the love of my life.
I know. And that just
makes this harder.
If I'm really honest,
it wasn't just goofy,
innocent Eric I fell for.
As vicious and
untrustworthy as
you can be...
There's a goodness in
you that breaks my heart...
Because a part of me
has always wanted you.
You won't be sorry.
I already am.
The time we had together
was unforgettable, but
it, it's over.
No, wait. It
doesn't have to be.
There is only one way
I see this ending...
And it's me walking
away with neither of you.
Don't do this.
Sookie.
This is the hardest decision
I've ever had to make...
(CRYING) But I know it's
the right one for all of
us. And so, please...
Don't try to stop
me, either of you.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WIND BLOWING)
(DISTORTED SOUNDS)
Jesus? Is that you?
(LOUD ZAPPING)
Oh, fuck, baby.
Look at you. Look what
I, I did. I'm... I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
What you mean, don't worry
about it? I killed you.
Everything's temporary.
Anyway, I probably would
have gotten cancer...
Died in a bed somewhere
with a nurse who doesn't
know half the shit I know.
Screwing up my IV's
and giving me bedsores.
I'm cool with
how things went.
But I sure the fuck ain't.
I murdered the man I love.
How am I supposed
to live with that?
Just keep breathing, baby.
It's that simple.
Mmm.
Jesus, wait.
Don't leave me.
Dude, I'm dead.
You're a medium.
I'll always be with you.
(ZAPPING)
(DISTORTED SOUNDS)
(CRYING)
ANDY: Miss Cleary.
Happy Halloween,
Sheriff Bellefleur.
Andy.
Sorry about the last time
when I took your flowers.
Mmm. That's okay.
You were nervous.
No, I was a drug
addict... V.
I thought I needed it to
do the job and to talk
pretty ladies like you...
So, I didn't feel like
a loser all the time.
It worked for awhile...
Then it didn't.
Okay, look, honey.
You're really sweet
and everything, but...
This is all just too
much for me right now.
It's no problem. Lot
of baggage, I get it.
I just wanted to say that
I'm sober, and I'm lonely.
And I can be good to
someone, if they let me.
'Night.
Sheriff Andy.
How about a hug?
I could really, really
use one tonight.
(MOANING)
You sure I can't
convince you to stay?
Tempting, but I don't really
think Emma's ready for that.
Oh.
So I'm going to take her
home and put her to bed.
Okay.
You and Emma are
the best thing...
Don't jinx it.
So now you're
superstitious?
I just, feel like...
If we are too
cute and cheesy...
That God is gonna drop
a brick on our heads.
Listen, I think
life is violent.
And cruel by nature...
So, when something good
comes along, you gotta
stop and celebrate it.
Be grateful.
Okay. Well, in that
case, you're welcome.
So are you.
Great.
Good night.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(GROWLING)
You're really leavin'?
Yup.
You know, if you didn't like
it, I can take direction.
No. I liked it.
I liked it a lot.
And maybe, uh...
Next time we
could try oral.
Uh, you know, Hoyt was kind
of shy about that, but...
I think maybe
'cause of my fangs.
Yeah, I'm, I'm down
for that. Just uh...
Jess, could we stop talkin'
about Hoyt so much?
Yeah, sorry. Sorry,
it's just all that I
got to compare this to.
Uh...
Fuck.
Do you think there's a part
of me that's, that's missin'?
Is that why you
don't want to stay?
What... No. Why
would you ask me that?
Uh...it's just
somethin' Hoyt said.
Thought we weren't
talkin' about him anymore.
Hey.
Yeah?
You're funny...
And you're excitin',
and you have...
The sexiest hip
bones I've ever seen.
I'm leavin' 'cause fucking
you made me hungry.
And I don't want to drink your
blood, 'cause I'm not ready to
be that intimate with you...
At least not yet.
So you're gonna glamour
some total stranger
and drink their blood?
Yeah.
(LAUGHING) Okay. I get it.
You know, it's, it's,
it's kinda like a
hooker with kissin'.
Not that you're
like a hooker.
Oh, well, maybe I
could pretend to be.
If you like that.
Hmm?
(LAUGHS)
You're like no other woman
I've ever been with.
And I have been
with a lot of women.
Oh God, that's so sweet.
(FANGS PROTRACT)
I'm sorry. I uh...
Low blood sugar.
(FANGS RETRACT)
I'll see you around.
(WHOOSH)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
JASON: Well, I knew
you'd be back.
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Reverend Newlin.
Trick or treat.
(FANGS PROTRACT)
(VAMPIRE GROWL)
When'd this happen?
Last night, the night
before. I don't remember.
I'm sorry, boss.
It's like somebody hit
delete in my brain.
Wait...
Fuck, you've
been glamoured.
Why would a vamper
want to glamour me?
Or dig a hole in the
damn parking garage?
Miss Flanagan, we've
been expecting you.
Hi, Nan. And gay
stormtroopers.
Perfect. Two
birds, one stone.
BILL: The Marnie situation
has been resolved, if that
makes any difference.
Ding dong, the witch
is dead. Yippee.
His Majesty showed great
leadership in extremely
perilous circumstances.
You should be
kissing his ring.
Why bother when your tongue's
already so far up his ass?
(DOOR CLOSES)
NAN: I wish for
one fucking night...
You could experience
the litany of bullshit
I've had to deal with.
NAN: Then you'd
have some idea of...
How little I give a
fuck about your small
town witch infestation.
Or your whole backwoods
kingdom, for that matter.
As someone who cares
so little, you seem
awfully pissed off.
Do I, Bill? Maybe that's
because I quit my fucking job!
You quit the AVL?
And the Authority.
No one quits
the Authority.
Quit, fired,
same difference.
We assumed we were the
ones to be terminated.
Oh, there's been an order
issued on your heads.
My last duty was supposed
to be delivering the true
death to both of you.
NAN: Of course, I
realized I'd be next.
I have been alive
for 816 years.
I refuse to be retired
like a fat first wife.
Let me make sure
I've got this straight.
You're mutinying against
the American Vampire
League and the Authority?
And you expect
us to join you?
We won't be alone.
There are factions inside
the regime who have never
been completely on board...
With the current agenda.
Sheriff Northman knows
what I'm talking about.
What's in it for us?
(LAUGHS)
NAN: Aside from
surviving the night?
How about your little
fairy waitress?
Oh, come on. The
mind reading, the
microwave fingers?
NAN: You didn't think
I knew what she was?
There are at least a couple
of thousand vampires...
Who would do almost anything
to get a taste of her blood.
Go ahead. She belongs
to neither of us.
She smells fantastic, but
that's hardly worth dying for.
You're bluffing.
I saw the way you
both looked at her.
Hungry puppy dogs,
slobbering over the
same juicy bone.
(WHOOSH)
(ERIC SCREAMS)
(THUDDING)
(SPLATTER)
You fucking...
(VAMPIRE SCREAM)
(BLOOD SPLATTERS)
(SCOWLS)
We are not fucking
puppy dogs!
(SCOWLS)
(FANGS RETRACT)
(SIGHS) What a bitch.
(TV PLAYING)
Tara? You
still awake?
Tara?
(GUN COCKS)
SOOKIE: Debbie?
SOOKIE: What
are you doin'?
DEBBIE: I should have done
this a long time ago.
TARA: Sookie!
(GUN FIRES)
(GLASS BREAKING)
(SCREAMING) Tara!
(GRUNTING)
(THUDDING)
(DEBBIE SCREAMS)
DEBBIE: No!
(GASPING) Oh, no.
Please don't.
Please don't kill me.
Please. Wait, no!
(GUN FIRES)
(SOOKIE SHREIKS)
SOOKIE: Tara, Tara.
(CRYING) Tara.
Oh God, Tara, no!
(CRYING) Tara, no!
Please, somebody help!
Please. Somebody
please help us!
SOOKIE: (SOBBING) Oh
God. Oh God. Somebody!
(ROCK SONG PLAYING)